

PEREZ, DAVID

MECHANICAL ENGINEER | WEBSITE: HTTPS://DALEJANDRO.COM

OBJECTIVE

GET A MASTER'S DEGREE IN M.E. AND WORK IN MY PROFESSION.

SKILLS

I am bilingual. I am a native Spanish speaker and I am also fluent in English.

I have worked with several engineering programs such as: AutoCAD, SolidWorks, Fusion 360, Mathcad, Ansys, LabView and MATLAB.

I work well under pressure and really capable socializing with all kinds of people.

EXPERIENCE

AUTOCAD DRAFTER • EASTERN ENGINEERING GROUP • 05/15/2018 - 07/15/2018

Providing support to our administrators and employees. Assisting in daily office needs and managing general administrative activities. Also, Improved AutoCAD knowledge and executed basic level tasks.

AUTOCAD DRAFTER • EASTERN ENGINEERING GROUP • 05/15/2019 - 07/15/2019

Performed research in critical new set of skills for the company and educated employees on the new utilities of AutoCAD like dynamic blocks that I had researched.

AUTOCAD DRAFTER • EASTERN ENGINEERING GROUP • 05/15/2020 - 07/15/2020

Got assigned with new projects from clients. Had to interact with clients to create a good proposal, then draw whatever was reflected on it and do the calculations to ensure that the structures worked under load. Finally submit the project to my supervisor.

EDUCATION

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA • MAY 2017 • RONALD REAGAN SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL

Graduated with a cumulative GPA of 3.75 and took AP classes like Calculus and Spanish. Also participated on the school's cross country and track & field teams.









PEREZ, DAVID

MECHANICAL ENGINEER | WEBSITE: HTTPS://DALEJANDRO.COM

BS IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING • MAY 2021 • JACKSONVILLE UNIVERSITY

I am pursuing my ME major at school. I currently have a 3.72 cumulative GPA and I am part of the sailing team on campus.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE OR LEADERSHIP

- Sailing captain of Coconut Grove Sailing Club 2015-2017
- Member of Hispanic Honor Society since 2015
- Assistant coach at Coconut Grove Sailing Club on summer 2017
- Member of Jacksonville Sailing team 2017-2020
- Captain of the Jacksonville Sailing team 2020





